[
    {"id":"1","question":"In Luke 1:13, what was the first thing the angel said to Zacharias?","choice1":"Do not be afraid","choice2":"I am Gabriel, You cannot speak","choice3":"You will make ready a people for the Lord","choice4":"","answer":"1"},
    {"id":"2","question":"According to Luke 1:41, what happened when Mary entered the house of Zacharias greeted Elizabeth?","choice1":"Zacharias was then able to speak","choice2":"Elizabeth was filled with the Holy Spirit","choice3":"An angel began to speak to them","choice4":"","answer":"2"},
    {"id":"3","question":"In Luke 1:76, Zacharias’ prophecy includes the statement, “And you, child, will be called the prophet of the Most High…”. Who is the child to which he is referring?","choice1":"John the Baptist","choice2":"Jesus","choice3":"Peter","choice4":"David","answer":"1"},
    {"id":"4","question":"According to Luke 2:43-44, how many days passed before Jesus’s parents realized He was not traveling with them as they returned home?","choice1":"1 day","choice2":"2 days","choice3":"3 days","choice4":"4 days","answer":"1"},
    {"id":"5","question":"In Luke 3:10-11, when the people asked John what they should do, what did he tell them to do?","choice1":"To pray for mercy","choice2":"To make crooked roads straight","choice3":"Whoever has two tunics should share with the person who has none","choice4":"Love your neighbor","answer":"3"},
    {"id":"6","question":"Which words of Jesus is an indication of Jesus establishing the Church?","choice1":"If you obey my voice and keep my covenant you will be my own possession","choice2":"You are a chosen race, royal priesthood and holy nation, people of God's own","choice3":"You are Peter and upon this rock I will build my Church","choice4":"","answer":"3"},
    {"id":"7","question":"What is the most significant aspect of Peter's confession in Caesarea Phililppi?","choice1":"Acknowledged Jesus as their Teacher","choice2":"Acknowledged  Jesus Christ as the Son of Living God","choice3":"Acknowledged Jesus as the Prophet","choice4":"Acknowledged Jesus as a good man","answer":"2"},
    {"id":"8","question":"What was Peter's response to Jesus question 'Who do people say that the Son of Man is?","choice1":"You are the Messiah, the Son of the Living God","choice2":"You are John the Baptist came back to life","choice3":"You are Jeremiah one of the Prophets","choice4":"","answer":"1"},
    {"id":"9","question":"Why do Abraham and Mary are the great models of faith?","choice1":"Because they both lived more than 2000 years ago","choice2":"Both believed in the Promise of God and submitted to the will of God","choice3":"Both received special messages from God","choice4":"","answer":"2"},
    {"id":"10","question":"How did God reveal Himself to the humanity in a unique way?","choice1":"Through the Ten Commandments","choice2":"Through the person of Jesus","choice3":"Through parting the Red Sea for Israelites","choice4":"","answer":"2"},
    {"id":"11","question":"Jesus began his public life by calling people to","choice1":"charity","choice2":"Repentance","choice3":"Love","choice4":"Mercy","answer":"2"},
    {"id":"12","question":"What is the meaning of Greek word 'Metanoia'","choice1":"Return","choice2":"Conversion","choice3":"Repent","choice4":"","answer":"1"},
    {"id":"13","question":"Faith is blindly  believing in a God who never revealed Himself to us","choice1":"True","choice2":"False","choice3":"","choice4":"","answer":"2"},
    {"id":"14","question":"Conversion is a call to return from wide sinful path to narrow fruitful path","choice1":"True","choice2":"False","choice3":"","choice4":"","answer":"1"},
    {"id":"15","question":"Christian faith has only one dimension and that is 'individual'","choice1":"True","choice2":"False","choice3":"","choice4":"","answer":"2"}
]